{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "家",
      "answer": "Jiā | family, home"
    },
    {
      "question": "几",
      "answer": "Jǐ | how many, how much"
    },
    {
      "question": "口",
      "answer": "Kǒu | a measure word mainly for the number of people in a family"
    },
    {
      "question": "照片",
      "answer": "Zhàopiàn | picture, photo"
    },
    {
      "question": "和",
      "answer": "Hé | and"
    },
    {
      "question": "个",
      "answer": "Gè | a measure word for general use"
    },
    {
      "question": "姐姐",
      "answer": "Jiějiě | elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "两",
      "answer": "Liǎng | two"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟弟",
      "answer": "Dìdì | younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "一共",
      "answer": "Yīgòng | altogether"
    },
    {
      "question": "还",
      "answer": "Hái | in additionl; still"
    },
    {
      "question": "妹妹",
      "answer": "Mèimei | younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "小",
      "answer": "Xiǎo | little, small"
    },
    {
      "question": "狗",
      "answer": "Gǒu | dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "当然",
      "answer": "Dāngrán | of course"
    },
    {
      "question": "张",
      "answer": "Zhāng | a measure word for flat objects"
    },
    {
      "question": "真",
      "answer": "Zhēn | real; really"
    },
    {
      "question": "可爱",
      "answer": "Kě'ài | lovely, cute"
    },
    {
      "question": "爱",
      "answer": "Ài | to love"
    },
    {
      "question": "没",
      "answer": "Méi | not"
    },
    {
      "question": "男",
      "answer": "Nán | male"
    },
    {
      "question": "做",
      "answer": "Zuò | to do, to be, to make"
    },
    {
      "question": "工作",
      "answer": "Gōngzuò | to work; work, job"
    }
  ]
}
